CLAIRE FLECKNEY

Software Developer

Lethbridge, AB

(403) 929-1237

claire.e.poulsen@gmail.com

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

A skilled and enthusiastic Programmer and Web Developer, experienced with HTML, CSS, JavaScript, C++, C#, SQL, Java, PHP, and Apache. Is in the process of learning React Native and Laravel in a classroom setting, as well as learning Python, React.js, and ASP.Net in an online, self-taught, environment.

EDUCATION —

Lethbridge College, Lethbridge, AB – CIT Program

2021 - Present

• 3.71 GPA

EXPERIENCE

September 2022 – Present Lead Front End Developer • SIT SOFTware

- Worked as part of a team to investigate the Business Needs of Precision Riding Academy
- Made decisions regarding procedures and accepted standard practices regarding front-end development
- Ensured proper internal and external documentation was kept during the course of project development

August 2014 – August 2021 Cabinet Installer • Full-Time • Triple M Housing Ltd

- Followed drawn plans to create finished kitchens
- Paid close attention to detail
- Ensured the finished product was aesthetically pleasing

KEY SKILLS -

- Proficient in multiple programming languages
- · Keen attention to detail
- Adaptable

COMMUNICATION

- Effectively communicates changes in plans and protocols both in person and online with SIT SOFTware team
- Able to describe operations in various coding languages in plain English and pseudocode